Schein, Donald; Papers apap209
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- 1966, Educational Television (Box 4 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1966, Elementary & Secondary Education Act (Box 4 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1966, Fundamentals of Television Production Syllabus (Box 4 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1966, Fundraising, 1966-1971 (Box 4 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1966, Income Tax (Box 4 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1966, Journal (Box 4 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1966, NAEB Journal (Periodical) (Box 4 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1966, Nelson Associates Study (Box 4 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1966, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 4 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1966, Nissen, Robert J., 1966-1967 (Box 4 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31)
- 1966, Pocket Notebook (Box 4 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 32)
- 1966, Satellite (Box 4 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 33)
- 1966, Scene on 17 (Program) (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1966, View (Periodical), 1966 December-1967 January (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1966, WHMT Internal Records (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1966, WHMT Internal Records (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1966, WHMT Internal Records (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1966, WHMT Internal Records (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1967, Diary (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1967, Educational Broadcasting Review (Periodical), 1967 October (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1967, Educational Television (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9-11)
- 1967, Estimated Cost of a Nationwide Educational Television System (Carnegie Commission Report) (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1967, Journal (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1967, Learning From Television: What The Research Says (NAEB Report) (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1967, The Long-Range Financing of Educational Television Stations (NAEB Conference Proceedings) (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1967, NAEB Journal (Periodical) (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1967, Nationals Citizens Committee for Public Television -- Press Packets (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17)
- 1967, News Clippings on WHMT (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18)
- 1967, New York Network (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1967, Public Broadcasting (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1967, Return to Nursing (Broadcast) (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1967, Scene on 17 (Program) (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1967, University of the Air (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1967, The View on Cablecasting and Educational Television (Periodical), 1967 April-1967 May (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1967, WMHT Internal Records (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25-27)
- 1968, Congressional Record of Act Creating Corporation for Public Broadcasting (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1968, Educational/Instructional Broadcasting (Periodical), 1968 June-1968 July (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1968, Electrography Producer's Manual (Publication) (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1968, Financial Potential Survey (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31)
- 1968, Fundamentals of Television Systems (NAEB Publication) (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 32)
- 1968, Journal (Box 5 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 33-34)
- 1968, National Citizen's Committee for Public Television (NCCT) (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1968, Nelson Associates Study (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1968, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1968, Public Broadcasting (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1968, Public Broadcasting (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1968, Scene on 17 [Program] (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1968, WMHT Internal Records (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1969, Annual Report (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1969, CPB Annual Report (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1969, Educational Broadcasting Review (Periodical), 1969 December (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1969, Educational Television (Periodical) (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1969, Gold, Bill (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1969, Journal (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1969, Kettering Conference on Public Television Programming (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1969, Mahrer, Neil -- Correspondence and Memoranda, 1969-1971 (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1969, Man is Destroying Himself: Can This Be Prevented? (Institute on Man and Science Report) (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1969, Membership Week Binder, 1969-1986 (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17-18)
- 1969, NAEB Convention Report (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1969, National Educational Television (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1969, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1969, Proposal For An Instructional Television Network: Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (RPI) and Union College (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1969. Public Broadcasting (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23-24)
- 1969, Scene on 17 (program) (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1969, Schenectady And The Arts (Pamphlet) (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1969, Study of State Public TV Systems For The Corporation For Public Broadcasting (Report) (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1969, SUNY Course on Educational Broadcasting (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1969, TV and Your Child: In Search of an Answer (TV Guide Report) (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1969, WMHT Internal Records (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1970, Eastern Educational Television Network Promotional Booklet (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31)
- 1970, Educational Broadcasting Review (Periodical), 1970 June-1970 August (Box 6 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 32)
- 1970, Educational/Instructional Broadcasting (Periodical) (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1970, Educational Television [Periodical] (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1970, Journal (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1970, NAEB Press Packet (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1970, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1970, Potential Impact of Cable Growth On Television Broadcasting (Ford Foundation Report) (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1970, Public Broadcasting (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7-10)
- 1970, Public Broadcasting Environment Center Pamphlet (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1970, The Real World of Technical Evolution in Broadband Communications (Sloan Commission Report) (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1970, Report of Second EBU Workshop for Producers and Directors of Television Programmes for Young People (European Broadcasting Union Report) (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1970, Rochester Area Educational Television Association (RAETA) (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1970, Saturday Review (Periodical) (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1970, Scene on 17 [Program] (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1970, Sesame Street Magazine, First Issue (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17)
- 1970, A Survey of Public Television Viewing in Eight Cities (CPB Report) (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18)
- 1970, To Improve Learning: A Report (Commission on Instructional Technology Report) (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1970, Volunteer Advisory Group (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1970, WMHT Internal Records (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1970, WMHT Internal Records (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1971, Educational Broadcasting Review (Periodical) (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1971, Educational/Instructional Broadcasting (Periodical), 1971 January (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1971, Educational Television (Periodical) (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1971, Journal (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1971, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1971, PBS Press Packet (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1971, Public Broadcasting (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29-30)
- 1971, Scene on Seventeen [Program] (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31-32)
- 1971, Schein, Donald -- Personnel File, 1971-1987 (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 33)
- 1971, Television and the Troubled Campus (TV Guide Report) (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 34)
- 1971, WMHT Internal Records (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 35)
- 1972, Campaign for PBS Board of Directors (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 36)
- 1972, The Children's Television Workshop: How and Why It Works (Report) (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 37)
- 1972, Columbia Journalism Review (Periodical), 1972 July-1972 August (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 38)
- 1972, Educational Broadcasting (Periodical), 1972 November-1972 December (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 39)
- 1972, Educational Broadcasting Review (Preprints) (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 40)
- 1972, Fundraiser Photos (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 41)
- 1972, The Humanist (Periodical), 1972 July-1972 August (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 42)
- 1972 [?], Journal (Box 7 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 43)
- 1972, Journal (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1972, "Man Builds, Man Destroys" (Series Guide) (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1972, Marketing in Nonprofit Organizations (Report) (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1972, Model Neighborhood Television School, Richmond, V.A. (Report) (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1972, National Public Affairs Center for Television (NPACT) (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1972, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1972, North of the Namaskeag: A Case Study in Viewer-Active Television (Maine Public Broadcasting Network Report) (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1972, PBS Board Meeting Binder, 1972 March (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1972, PBS Program Standards and Practices (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1972, Program Policy, 1972-1979 (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1972, Public Broadcasting (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11-16)
- 1972, Scene on Seventeen (Programs) (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17-18)
- 1972, They Got It Together: A Collection of 100 Outstanding Public Television Promotional Ideas (CPB Report) (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1972, Two Studies of the Audience of WJCT-TV: Jacksonville, FL, Focusing on the Viewers of Feedback (CPB Report) (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1972, Who Watched The Electric Company? (Children's Television Workshop Report) (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1972, WMHT Internal Records (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1972, National Public Affairs Center for Television (NPACT) (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1973, The Center (Periodical), 1973 May-1973 June (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1973, Daily Notes [?] (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1973, The Future of Educational Telecommunication: A Planning Study (U.S. Government Report) (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1973, Journal (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1973, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1973, Overview of the Office of Telecommunications Policy (Committee Hearing Report) (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1973, PBS National Meeting, Baltimore (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1973, Public Broadcasting (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31-34)
- 1973, Public Telecommunications Review (Periodical), 1973 December (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 35)
- 1973, Public Television Station Projected Operations and Costs (NAEB Report) (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 36)
- 1973, Rate Cards and Related Material, 1973-1986 (Box 8 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 37)
- 1973, Report of the Task Force on the Long-Range Financing of Public Broadcasting (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1973, WMHT Internal Records (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1973, The WMHT Program Guide (Program) (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1973, The WMHT Program Guide (Program) (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1974, Community Survey: San Jose, California (CPB Report) (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1974, Essentials for Effective Minority Programming In Public Broadcasting (CPB Report) (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1974, Getting to Sesame Street: Origins of the Children's Television Workshop (Publication) (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1974, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1974, Newspaper Profile of Donald Schein (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1974, NOVA Promotional Packet (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1974, The People's Business (Periodical) (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1974, Preserving the Moving Image (Corporation for Public Broadcasting Report) (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1974, Public Broadcasting (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1974, Journal (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1974, Public Broadcasting (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15-16)
- 1974, Public Telecommunications Review (Periodical) (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17-18)
- 1974, Snell, DeWitt S. (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1974, State Of The Art: A Study of Current Practices and Trends in Educational Uses of Public Radio and Television (CPB Report) (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1974, The Video Implosion: Models for Reinventing Television (ASPEN Institute Report) (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1974, WMHT Internal Records (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1974, WMHT-FM Program Policy (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1974, The WMHT Program Guide (Program) (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24-26)
- 1975, Access (Periodical) (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1975, Corporation for Public Broadcasting Annual Report (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1975, Eastern Educational Television Network (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1975, Empire State College (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1975, Journal (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31)
- 1975, Maday, Charles -- Memoranda, 1975-1976 (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 32)
- 1975, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 33)
- 1975, PBS Round Robin (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 34)
- 1975, Public Broadcasting (Box 9 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 35)
- 1975, Public Broadcasting (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1-2)
- 1975, Public Broadcasting Financing Act of 1975 (Congressional Hearing Report) (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1975, Public Broadcasting in the United States (PBS White Paper) (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1975, Public Broadcasting in the Unites States: A White Paper (PBS Publication) (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1975, Public Telecommunications Review (Periodical) (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1975, Public Television: Toward Higher Ground: Report and Papers From the Aspen Institute Conference on Public Broadcasting (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1975, Rotary Brochure on Schein Speech (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1975, Telecommunications Policy Research Conference Proceedings (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1975, TeleVisions (Periodical), 1975 August-1975 September (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1975, WMHT Internal Records (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11-13)
- 1975, The WMHT Program Guide (Program) (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14-15)
- 1976, Access (Periodical) (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16-17)
- 1975, Archaeology Project, 1976-1977 (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18)
- 1976, Board of Trustees (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1976, Day-Timers, 1976 January-1976 June (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1976, Day-Timers, 1976 July-1976 December (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1976, Eastern Educational Television Network -- Board Meeting, 1976 June (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1976, Journal (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1976, Machold, Nancy, 1976-1986 (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24-25)
- 1976, Maday, Charles -- Notes and Memoranda (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1976, NAEB Chicago Conference [?] (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1976, NAEB Harvard Program (Box 10 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28-29)
- 1976, NAEB Harvard Program (Box 11 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1-2)
- 1976, NAEB Harvard Program [?] (Box 11 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3-5)
- 1976, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 11 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1976, Open Education for the People (Educational Broadcasting Corporation Report) (Box 11 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1976, PBS Informational Binder [?] (Box 11 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1976, Public Broadcasting (Box 11 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9-14)
- 1976, Public Telecommunications Review (Periodical) (Box 11 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1976, Public Telecommunications Review (Box 11 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1976, Singer, Art-Notes and Memoranda (Box 11 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17)
- 1976, A Study of Public Television's Educational Services (Corporation for Public Broadcasting Report), 1975-1976 (Box 11 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18)
- 1976, Television Quarterly (Periodical), Winter 1976-1977 (Box 11 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1976, WMHT-FM Personnel Binder, 1976-1982 (Box 11 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20-21)
- 1976, WMHT Internal Records (Box 11 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1976, WMHT Internal Records (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1976, The WMHT Program Guide (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2-3)
- 1977, Access (Periodical) (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1977, CPB Public Television Survey: On-Air Fundraising (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1977, Day-Timers, 1977 January-1977 June (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1977, Day-Timers, 1977 July-1977 December (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1977, Desk Register, 1977-1978 (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1977, Development Sections Weekly Reports (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1977, Educational And Industrial Television (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1977, Fitzpatrick, Angela, 1977-1986 (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1977, Human Resources Training and Development: Selected Models for Training of Radios and Television Broadcast Personnel (Corporation for Public Broadcasting Report) (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1977, Instructional Television: A Study (WDSE Report) (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1977, Journal (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1977, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1977, PBS Statement Before the Federal Communications Commission in the Matter of Commission Policy Concerning the Noncommercial Nature of Educational Broadcast Systems (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1977, Public Broadcasting (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17-20)
- 1977, Public Telecommunications Review (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21-22)
- 1977, Research Guidelines for Programming Decision Makers: A Programmers Guide to the Dynamics of Radio (Arbitration Report) (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1977, RISE (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1977, Six Experiments in Ascertainment Methodology (CPB Report) (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1977, WMHT Internal Records (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26-27)
- 1977, The WMHT Program Guide (Box 12 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28-29)
- 1978, Access (Periodical) (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1978, Capital Equipment File (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- 1978, CPB Memoranda to Station Managers (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- 1978, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1978 September-1978 December (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1978, Educational and Industrial Television (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1978, Future of Public Broadcasting Conference (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
  (Includes Audiocassette).
- 1978, Human Services Planning Council Award (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1978, Journal (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1978, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1978, NOAA Weather Radio Network (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1978, Patterns of Performance: Public Broadcasting and Education, 1974-1976 (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
  CPB Publication.
- 1978, PBS Memoranda to Station Managers (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1978, PBS Planning Conference (Williamsburg, VA) (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)
- 1978, PBS Press Releases (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1978, Public Broadcasting (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15-20)
- 1978, The Public Broadcasting News (Periodical), 1978 October (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1978, Public Participation in Public Broadcasting (CPB Task Force Report) (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1978, Public Telecommunications Review (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23-24)
- 1978, Public TV and the Press (PBS Report) (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1978, Reports and Publications on Public Broadcasting (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1978, Saratoga Performing Arts Center (SPAC), 1978-1986 (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1978, Tangarone, Anthony (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1978, TIAA-CREF Annual Report (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1978, WMHT Auction Alternatives (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1978, WMHT Board of Trustees (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31)
- 1978, WMHT Internal Records (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 32-34)
- 1978, The WMHT Program Guide (Box 13 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 35-38)
- 1979, Access, Periodical (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- 1979, A Survey of Voter Attitudes Towards Public Television in the State of New York, Study (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2-3)
- 1979, Capital Equipment File, 1979-1987 (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- 1979, Community Advisory Board (?) Binder (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- 1979, Corporation for Public Broadcasting Survey (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6)
- 1979, CPB Development Newsletter (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- 1979, CPB Memoranda to Station Managers (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- 1979, CPB Reports (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 January (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 February (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 March (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 April (Box 14 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13)